{"Input question": "Who was 16th president of the United States?", "Exact Answer": "Lincoln", "Supporting sentence": "On November 6, 1860, Lincoln was elected the 16th president of the United States.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When did Amazon surpass Walmart as the most valuable retailer in the United States by market capitalization?", "Exact Answer": "1862", "Supporting sentence": "The National Union Party was united by Lincoln's support for emancipation.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Where is Apple's satellite campus?", "Exact Answer": "Japan", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who founded AT&T?", "Exact Answer": "Alton", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When did Warren Buffett begin buying stock in Berkshire Hathaway?", "Exact Answer": "1930", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Where did the Kuomintang-led government retreat?", "Exact Answer": "United States", "Supporting sentence": "He preserved the Union, abolished slavery, strengthened the federal government, and modernized the U.S. economy.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who was appointed CEO of Citibank North America by Weill and Reed?", "Exact Answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "Supporting sentence": "Franklin D. Roosevelt, preparing America for war, used the words of the Civil War president to clarify the threat posed by Germany and Japan.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When was Adams-On\u00eds Treaty between the United States and Spain defined?", "Exact Answer": "1930", "Supporting sentence": "The National Union Party was united by Lincoln's support for emancipation.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Where was Elon Musk born?", "Exact Answer": "Springfield", "Supporting sentence": "Robert Todd Lincoln was born in 1843 and Edward Baker Lincoln (Eddie) in 1846.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who founded SpaceX?", "Exact Answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When did a genetic test determin Oprah Winfrey's matrilineal line?", "Exact Answer": "1830", "Supporting sentence": "Despite this, when Lincoln asked what Grant's plans were, the general replied, \"I propose to fight it out on this line if it takes all summer.\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Where did Oprah Winfrey begin attending Lincoln High School?", "Exact Answer": "Maryland", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who was both the youngest news anchor and the first black female news anchor at Nashville's WLAC-TV?", "Exact Answer": "Lincoln", "Supporting sentence": "Burton argues that Lincoln's republicanism was taken up by the emancipated Freedmen.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When was Richardson city originally incorporated?", "Exact Answer": "1930", "Supporting sentence": "Lincoln's flag-enfolded body was then escorted in the rain to the White House by bareheaded Union officers, while the city's church bells rang.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Where does Vent-A-Hood have their corporate headquarter?", "Exact Answer": "Lincolniana", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who was Steve Jobs' biological father?", "Exact Answer": "Samuel Lincoln", "Supporting sentence": "He was an affectionate, though often absent, husband and father of four children.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When did Steve Jobs die?", "Exact Answer": "1800", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Where did Lincoln family move to out of fear of a milk sickness outbreak?", "Exact Answer": "Todds", "Supporting sentence": "In early March 1830, partly out of fear of a milk sickness outbreak, several members of the extended Lincoln family moved west to Illinois, a free state, and settled in Macon County, 10 miles (16 km) west of Decatur.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who was Steve Jobs' adoptive father?", "Exact Answer": "Samuel Lincoln", "Supporting sentence": "He was an affectionate, though often absent, husband and father of four children.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "When did Washington D.C.'s population had grown 75% from the previous census?", "Exact Answer": "1860", "Supporting sentence": "Lincoln received 1,866,452 votes, or 39.8% of the total in a four-way race.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who led Apple's aquisition of NeXT?", "Exact Answer": "Lincoln", "Supporting sentence": "Pennsylvania put him over the top, led by Pennsylvania iron interests who were reassured by his tariff support.", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}{"Input question": "Who is Abraham Lincoln's ancestor from Hingham?", "Exact Answer": "Schwartz", "Supporting sentence": "Americans asked, \"What would Lincoln do?\"", "Supporting Wikipedia Document": "AbrahamLincoln.txt"}